Interviewer: Where were you born?
Rebecca: I was born in Italy.
Interviewer: Do you have family there?
Rebecca: Yes, all my family lives there.
Interviewer: Where do you live now?
Rebecca: I live in the UK.
Interviewer: Where in the UK?
Rebecca: I live in Newcastle.
Interviewer: Did you go out last weekend?
James: Er, yes, I did.
Interviewer: What did you do?
James: Er, I went with some friends to a pub, um,
in Banbury, a town near here, and we watched a band. It was really good.
Interviewer: What’s your favourite room in your house?
Maura: Probably my bedroom. I love sleeping.
Interviewer: Can you describe it?
Maura: Er, yes, it’s got a bed and two bedside tables, a wardrobe,
and a chest of drawers.
Interviewer: What did you do yesterday evening?
Asya: Last night I had dinner with my brother in Brooklyn.
Interviewer: What time did you go to bed?
Asya: I went to bed around 1.00 a.m.
Interviewer: What did you do on New Year’s Eve last year?
David: So, last, last New Year’s Eve, my wife and I, we met some friends in
downtown New York, in Manhattan.
We went to a very nice steakhouse, and then went for some cocktails,
and er, sang in the New Year in, er, in New York.
Interviewer: Did you have a good time?
David: We had a very, very good time.